You mean you also gave him some sub-advice?
I was so much busier then.
That's amazing.
It's gone.
Good night.
Good night. - Good night.
Isn't your hair shiny today?
Like the oil I got for my birthday, even though I want it.
But it's not shiny.
It's not shiny.
It's like you haven't washed your hair in a while.
I wonder if it's a fake.
Maybe just a little bit.
If you iron your hair with it, it'll stay shiny for a long time.
I see. So it's not something you have to leave on all the time.
I see... I've learned something else.
If you iron it with that, it'll be super smooth and silky.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm just making small talk.
It's really just small talk.
By the way, we'd like to get on with the recording first.
And then we'll talk to you later.
This week.
I'd like to...
At first, it seemed like we were going over the flowers.
Is there any chance this could be...
You know, the kind of thing where you wake up in the morning and you're not feeling so good.
I don't know.
It's cold. It's just mornings.
Only in the mornings.
And at night, I go to bed with the air conditioning on.
Wow, air conditioning is a little dangerous this time of year.
Maybe it's too soon.
I'm going to be dead in a heartbeat.
That's why I'm asking you all to take care of yourselves.
Please be careful.
It's really hot and humid. I'm really sure it's just so tantalizing.
I can sleep, right?
It's so humid, isn't it?
It rained too much yesterday.
It was so sweltering.
It's not so much that it's hot.
It's more like hot and humid.
Sweltering.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can't help it.
It's times like this when I'm in pain
I've been in a lot of pain.
It's times like this that I dare you to wear heavy clothes.
Good evening.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's that time of year, isn't it?
Are you feeling all right?
I'm fine.
Scoble.
You really don't seem like you'll catch a cold.
No, I'm fine.
I'm weak.
Rags.
How do you say that?
It's just when you need it the most, it's so shabby.
Because you're slow.
It's a swim.
That's right.
That's why this time, that's why I started gargling my nose
Nasal gargle is super good.
It's very good.
I did it twice a day.
That's right.
Before I go out, or after I wake up.
After going out. He said he was done with his trip.
He said, “Uh-oh.
“Uh-oh.
Saying, “Uh-oh.
That's so loud.
He's like, “Oh, my God.” He's like, “Oh, my God.
It's like they're celebrating your birthday.
It's like if you don't say it, it'll backfire on you.
That's right.
I see.
But the guests are also interested in MY.
That's right.
The guests are here, and we're doing it now.
Licher.
You know, when I'm on stage, when I'm thinking, “Oh my God, something's wrong...
If you think there's a flower in the air and you press it, it's like, “Oh, my God!
And the next day, it's like...
No, no, no... it's fine if he's here.
I'm sure they sell those sets inside.
I'm not a civilian.
First of all, I'd like to share with you a quote from a woman... this is...
Mae West, the great actress... yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes, Mae West, yes...
She was born in 1893.
She was born in the 19th century and was very active in the early 20th century.
Oh, boo-boo!
She was born in the 19th century and was very famous in the 19th and early 20th century, and she was very famous in the 19th and early 20th century.
I'm sure you'll be interested in it right away.
Don't cry for the man who left you.
The next guy might fall in love with your smile.
There it is.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Even if you're heartbroken
The next guy will fall in love with your smile.
I want to be able to say that I want to be a grown-up... why not... why not just say it right out loud?
I've seen him say some other things, but he's just a little bit godlike.
I'm not just saying quotes, I'm usually saying quotes, like good morning, not good morning.I'm not just talking about quotes, I'm talking about the usual, and I'm not just talking about quotes, I'm talking about things like “Good morning”, not “Good morning”.
I'm sure the sun rises in the morning, so this day is coming every day.
I think you really live your life like that.
I'll live like this, too.
I'm going to go with...
That's a great word.
Who's there?
Who's there? Nitty, isn't it?
Nitty's got 500 bars to give away.
If you deliver the bars to Shizuoka, we'll give you 1,500 bars.
I'll have to say “bar” 1,500 times!
Thank you, Mr. 52nd grader from Suzuka City, Mie Prefecture!
He's 63, so he's a senior.
I'll run and buy yakisoba bread.
If I tell him I'm not a senior and I'll kill him, he'll start talking about it.
I'm not a senior, so if I tell them I'm going to kill them, they'll start talking about it.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a place for your grandchildren and grandchildren and grandchildren and grandchildren and grandchildren
I have a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandson and a grandchild!
It's...
Eh, first of all, it's some
Eh, first of all, it's some...
There it is...
Oh!
You're here, aren't you?
To conjnea
enjoujou get your eyes strained.
enjoujou get your eyes吩 I can't but you need to do something about it
But I need your help
But I need to know that you have a good reason for your arm to be in the competition for the eve10jan
I need to get a good arm to compete with my rivals in eve10jan
I've got a great rivalry with my 10 best competitors
I'm pretty cool.
I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure I'm pretty sure
Many people who say that are like that
He's doing his best. Subie's great, too... he's so expressive.
He's got a great reaction. Like a foreigner.
But there's a reason for that. But there's a reason for that.
So, when we were talking about how it's difficult to tell a story, and how you should have a reaction to the story, because if you're listening to it in a blank stare, you'll look like a dope.
And then I was next to him and he was like, “Wow!
That was too good! I thought it was too good to be true, and it lit a fire under me.
There was a time when it was so great that Maya and I said, “Hey, Nanaka's ready, she's probably fine now.
But that became the norm.
Yes, I did.
So, Mr. Subie, you're already in middle school...
Mr. 52nd grader, the way you put in your sentences is amazing!
I like the fresh green weather...
Master Riah, I'm glad to hear that your part-timer, Ebitu-chan, is doing well.
Thank you very much!
The other day, I went for a walk in Provence, and the scenery turned out to be very nice...
Master!
Provence!
How do you like it?
That's a great word for it.
It's like this.
Oh, yes.
Provence.
The South of France, France.
This is really Provence.
Southern France
This is Provence.
Something here.
It's a Millet painting, right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Something like this.
Like this.
Like this... like this...
A UFO.
This...
What was it?
A crop circle.
Yes, yes, yes, yes...
I wonder why so many people come this time of year?
I wonder why so many people are here this time of year.
Wheat. wheat
Even though it's fresh green weather.
It is, isn't it?
Wheat?
Is this Korean?
Wheat.
Hatake-wise.
Yes.
This is a great view.
Is this Japan?
Mie Prefecture.
Mie Prefecture?
Mie like this?
Like France.
You can see the scenery.
It's nice, a walk.
It would be nice to have such a view on a walk.
I'll put a phrase on it.
I'll take a phrase.
No, no, no...
You typed it yourself.
I'll take a look at the scenery, too.
Yes, sir.
Then let's start with a haiku... by our Matsuo Basho.
Matsuo Basho?
Yes, sir.
Kanamugiya.
Kinmugiya
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Uh, tired of walking
Tired of walking
Yes, I'm tired of walking
I'll take a Nomsa.
I'm suddenly a year old since I started уть
I'm getting boo-boo'd and I'm falling down... 25 sen version. Boo Boo and Fall Tenyo Naho Naho Naho - 25 sen edition
here Lou
theatrical Mr. Nita sometimes
Well, well, well, well.
I heard it's harvest time for wheat.
Really?
That's why.
So it is.
You don't see many wheat fields around here, do you?
No, I don't.
I don't remember much.
Rice paddies?
That's right.
Yes, but...
I see... that's it then.
Udon noodles?
That's right.
Wheat, for example.
I thought it was all beer.
It is, isn't it?
Flour.
Yes, yes, yes.
And the other thing...
This is good, too.
Arakawa-ku, Tokyo
Dancing Nippori Ebi-buddy!
Thank you very much.
Genius Master
Yes, sir.
Cheerful Servon
Beautiful Ebituaries.
Oh!
Elegant.
What kind of service shot is this?
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna charge you for this. I'm gonna charge you for this.
I'll pay you.
Here you go.
That's right.
I'll have you pay for it.
With this.
Bow.
Vow.
Bow. About 50,000.
Bow 50,000.
Bau 50,000
Coman Bau.
Bau 50,000 bau.
So...
Good evening, Nebo.
What a surprise!
This is Arakawa-ku, right here.
It's downtown.
Really...
I once wrote a song about Nippori.
When I wrote a song about Nippori
I walked around this neighborhood
It's really interesting.
I envy you.
It was nice.
Yes, it was.
There are a lot of nice, small stores.
There are so many nice, small shops.
What's more, over here...
Most of them are concentrated in one place.
In the downtown area...
There's a coexistence of the old and the new.
And the new ones coexist.
That's right.
There are those who know and those who know. In the know and in the know.
Suddenly, it's like a bolt from the blue.
What is this?
Like it's from the Showa era.
It's just like that.
There's a famous shop in his neighborhood.
There's a famous store for daikaimo in his neighborhood.
I love daiaimo!
And right next door to this daikagaimo store
There's also an oden shop right next to the daikagaimo shop!
That's great!
The combination of the two makes no sense at all!
The fact that there's a daikaimo store and an oden shop together...
It doesn't make sense!
I don't get it.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's Japanese food, though.
I knew it... downtown is interesting.
By the way, there's a takaimo shop.
When you order, they pour honey on it.
And they sprinkle sesame seeds.
The simple taste of the sweet potato...
You can eat as much as you want after lunch.
If you like, by all means.
Why don't you just dip your chopsticks in it and eat it in a circular motion?
Yes, it's delicious, so is the honey!
So he sent me a picture of the outside of the store.
It's also very nice.
It's kind of...
It's a bit Showa-era, isn't it?
It's nice.
Let's see...
May I?
Now that I'm being rushed.
There you go.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's nice.
We're pretty much in the same genre when it comes to this. It's pretty much the same genre when it comes to this.
Right?
Yeah.
Cute.
Shitamachi
Maybe it's that.
It's a dare by the same owner.
It's like a college sweet potato.
The typeface is a bit similar.
That's right.
Daigaku imo in Tokyo.
Why does “Daigaku” stand for “University”?
Wasn't it something like that?
Some university...
What was it?
A school cafeteria?
Yes, it's like they made them in the cafeteria.
That's right.
I mean, how did it start?
There are places like the University of Tokyo, for example.
I see.
I think so.
So that's why they call it the college sweet potato.
Yes...
That's funny!
Next time, if it comes up in high school, if it's a high school sweet potato...
No, it's true.
If it's from middle school, it's a middle school sweet potato.
There's elementary school sweet potato?
Kindergarten sweet potato
It's like sweet potatoes.
huh?
I see.
I see... interesting.
Ah, sweet potatoes.
Wow!
That's good!
That's not good! This is so bad!
Wow!
What's shining so brightly?
I love it!
I love these crispy candies.
And this one too.
And this one.
And these too.
I like college potatoes too.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
When I was a little kid, I was so happy when I had a takaimo in my lunch box.
No, I understand.
Like this.
Wow!
I don't think I'll ever get one.
I bet they look delicious.
I bet they look delicious!
It's nice to have a place like this in the neighborhood.
I'm jealous!
Oh, it was chosen as the Arakawa souvenir by Arakawa Ward residents!
What?
It's been chosen as the best souvenir of Arakawa by Arakawa Ward residents!
If you go to Arakawa, you must have this!
I ate it!
I love it!
Looks delicious!
Thank you very much.
Thanks for your hard work.
You must be happy now.
I love the potato car.
It's so dusty.
No, it's true.
But a soba car... an imo car...
I have a warm feeling. It's so simple. What a warm feeling. I like the simplicity of it.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Also, last week...
Sappon's partner...
Mariko...
I was wondering if you could give Mariko a devil name.
So we decided to call her Mona Lisa.
Surprisingly, everyone liked it.
They drew a picture for me right away.
Thank you, Kengoro Miyake!
The master and his part-timer, Mr. Ebichu.
Good evening, Devil.
This time, we have a regular customer, Ms. Kawasaki, aka Mona Lisa, and her godmother, Mariko.
And my godmother, Mariko.
I drew this.
I'm so happy to hear that.
This is how it looks like...
It's so similar! It's so similar!
Shingo, you look so much like him
Shingo, I've never called you Shingo
Shingo.
We're in the same class.
Shingo's like you.
You look like Shingo.
Shingo, you look like Shingo
Shingo, I think it's an event and a jump rope pull.
You're right.
He's got great eyes, doesn't he?
Yes, they are.
Well, well, well.
godfather
It's nice.
I wonder why Mona Lisa.
Next time Mariko comes over.
You heard her.
It's probably nothing.
It's just an idea that popped into my head. I'm saying it just popped into my head.
There's got to be some kind of motive.
It's like a four-letter word.
Like, “This is the only thing I could think of right now.
It was the Mona Lisa.
That's amazing.
He has great sensitivity.
Well, well, well.
What do you think?
We got a lot of devil's charges.
That's the one the staff wants.
Sardis shot.
Yay, I'll take it!
Thank you very much.
First of all, Yuuhi-san from Zatar.
I want you to do your best on the stage.
I'll do my best.
I met Zatar in Kawasaki the other day.
Really?
He said, “Oh, my God!
She said, “Oh, my God!
Say “Ow!
He said, “Oh, my God!
You know... everyone comes to Ebitu-chan's live, don't they?
“Oh, oh, oh!
“Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
When I see them on the way back home...
he tells me his handle, or whatever you call it.
Say, “Oh, oh!
She says, “Oh, oh, oh, oh.
He's like, “Oh, I'm Yuuhi of Zatar.
Like, “I'm Yuhi of Zatar.
Like, “You're Zatar's Yuuhi.
mmmmmmmmmm
Wow!
I'm glad you feel safe. I'm glad you feel safe.
I'm glad, glad, glad.
I've heard on the radio that people are getting a lot of handshakes, so it's something like that.
Right?
It's like you're a celebrity.
I feel like I'm famous.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There was a blue Mars, too, come to think of it.
Oh!
Oh.
And, uh...
I don't know if I can do this.
Hmm
fufu (Japanese for “fufu”)
I'm on the ground
The day is
Shiranui ne
Shiranai Kai
Hee
Hoshina bau
baa
Happy birthday, Bari-kata-chan!
birthday without you
You are in the middle of your birthday
It's right...
Yes
Thank you
It's about 29th of May, right?
Today's the day.
And today, right?
You're doing it in the morning?
Wow!
I'd like to see it.
Have you seen them? You've seen them before?
I've seen them too.
I've also seen them at the birthday party of a friend of mine
It's interesting to see their personalities come out in their own colors.
So I'm doing it, and the way I'm allowed to do it is that I sing and do all the mc's by myself.
So you do all the mc's too?
I'm still in school...
And to Mr. Bälz, I wish you a speedy recovery of your throat
You really do have a lot of flowers, don't you?
Yes, yes, yes.
And a door... and a brother... from college...
It's said to have originated in Hongo, where there were many universities during the Meiji Era
I'm sure there are a lot of theories about the origin of Hongo.
I'm sure you're not the only one who's had a good time in the past.
I'm not saying that you two are getting smarter, are you?
The speed of the live broadcasts is really good.
After I said that, I realized that there are good things and bad things about being human.
I thought I'd better refrain from doing so, but...
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha...
I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star.
Finish it, finish it, finish it.
Thank you very much.
Five million.
Five million, isn't it?
End, end, end, end, end, end, end, end.
Thank you for dinner.
Bon appétit.
Thank you very much.